John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Personal, 1930-1986, undated; 7
  - Legal, 1930-1958, undated; 3
    - No. 201: Minnie D. Gresham-Will, 1946-1949 (Box 444, Folder 19)
    - No. 203: Tommie W. Clark-Adoption of Eloise, 1948 (Box 444, Folder 20)
    - No. 204: Lena Urquhart-Dependent Children, 1948-1951 (Box 444, Folder 21)
    - No. 206: Horace Rogers, 1948 (Box 444, Folder 22)
    - No. 207: Political Advertisements, 1945-1951 (Box 444, Folder 23)
    - No. 208: Political Ads-Opponent, 1945-1951 (Box 444, Folder 24)
    - No. 209: Political Race Results, 1944 (Box 444, Folder 25)
    - No. 210: Lee Herndon, 1948-1949 (Box 444, Folder 26)
    - No. 212A: Anderson County Grand Jury, 1949-1950 (Box 444, Folder 27)
    - No. 212B: Anderson County Grand Jury, 1949-1950 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - No. 213A: Houston County Grand Jury, 1949-1950 (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - No. 213B: Houston County Grand Jury, 1949-1950 (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - No. 214: State of Texas v. Tom Kent (Liquor Injunction), 1950 (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - No. 215: Henderson County Grand Jury, 1949-1950 (Box 445, Folder 5)
    - No. 216: Pearlie Evelyn Heard, 1948 (Box 445, Folder 6)
    - No. 219: Wiley McGee, 1949 (Box 445, Folder 7)
    - No. 220: Bobbie Ray Clarl & Joe Leeta Clark-Divorce, 1948-1951 (Box 445, Folder 8)
    - No. 222: Rosie Smith c/o Riley Hatcher, 1948-1949 (Box 445, Folder 9)
    - No. 224: Fred Gilliam, 1948-1949 (Box 445, Folder 10)
    - No. 227: General, 1949-1950 (Box 445, Folder 11)
    - No. 229: Dixie Haynes, 1949 (Box 445, Folder 12)
    - No. 231: Vivian Brown v. Raymond Brown (Divorce), 1949 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - No. 232: Davis, Turner & Caruthers v. W.M. Pirtle, 1949-1951 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - No. 233: Ophelia Cook & Marvin Cook-Divorce, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 3)
    - No. 235: G.H. Birdwell-Estate, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - No. 236: Associates Investment Company v. Wiley Pennell, Jr. & W.S. Pruitt, 1949-1950 (Box 446, Folder 5)
    - No. 237: Mystik Sales, 1949-1950 (Box 446, Folder 6)
    - No. 238: G.L. Frazier, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 446, Folder 7)
    - No. 239: Helen Palmer & C.L. Palmer-Divorce, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 8)
    - No. 240: William McKinley Holloway-Murder, 1948 (Box 446, Folder 9)
    - No. 241: Milas M. Wallace-Removal of Minor’s Disabilities, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 10)
    - No. 242: Faye B. McNair-Removal of Disabilities of Coverture, 1949 (Box 446, Folder 11)
    - No. 243: Lueaster & Richard Dightman-Divorce, 1949-1950, 1958 (Box 446, Folder 12)
    - No. 244: Effie McCoy v. John B Valentine (Child Support Contempt), 1949 (Box 446, Folder 13)
    - No. 245: Herman Simpson v. Fannie Mae Simpson (Divorce), 1949 (Box 446, Folder 14)
    - No. 246: Vivian Hill v. Earl Hill (Divorce), 1949 (Box 446, Folder 15)
    - No. 248: (E.F. McRae vs.) W.P. (Bud) Morrison-Palamino Dispute, 1949-1950 (Box 446, Folder 16)
    - No. 249: Willie Jackson Wilks v. John T. Wilks (Divorce), 1949 (Box 446, Folder 17)
    - No. 251A: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 446, Folder 18)
    - No. 251B: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 446, Folder 19)
    - No. 251C: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 446, Folder 20)
    - No. 251D: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 446, Folder 21)
    - No. 251E: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 446, Folder 22)
    - No. 251F: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - No. 251G: C.E. Harkey, 1950-1952 (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - No. 252: Forrest E. Vanderpool, 1949-1950 (Box 447, Folder 3)
    - No. 253: Joe Al Huff (State v. Jimmie Frizzell)-Murder, 1949-1950 (Box 447, Folder 4)
    - No. 254: Kiwanis Club Inc., 1950 (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - No. 255: Sylvester Wynfield-Injunction, 1949-1951 (Box 447, Folder 6)
    - No. 256: Texas Fiddler’s Association, 1950 (Box 447, Folder 7)
    - No. 257: Jeanette Porter v. Kenneth J. Porter (Divorce), 1950 (Box 447, Folder 8)
    - No. 258: Daniel Paul Ballard-Adoption, 1950, 1954 (Box 447, Folder 9)
    - No. 259: Joe Tom Miller-Misappropriations, 1950 (Box 447, Folder 10)
    - No. 260: Hattie Browning-Will, 1950 (Box 447, Folder 11)
    - No. 261: Scott Crawford-Collections, 1950-1951 (Box 447, Folder 12)
    - No. 262: Helen Graham-Child Support, 1950 (Box 447, Folder 13)
    - No. 263: Alma Pate v. Butler Publishing Company, 1950-1951 (Box 447, Folder 14)
    - No. 264: Johnnie Suter, Big Spring, TX, 1948-1951 (Box 447, Folder 15)
    - No. 265: A.C. Kownslar, 1948-1951 (Box 448, Folder 1)
    - No. 266A: J.J. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 448, Folder 2)
    - No. 266B: J.J. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 448, Folder 3)
    - No. 266C: J.J. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 448, Folder 4)
    - No. 266D: J.J. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 448, Folder 5)
    - No. 266E: J.J. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 448, Folder 6)
    - No. 266F: J.J. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 448, Folder 7)
    - No. 267: Mutual Insurance (local), 1949 (Box 448, Folder 8)
    - No. 268: Elizabeth Carla Avery, et al.-Dependent Children, 1950 (Box 448, Folder 9)
    - No. 269: Allene Phillips & Ralph Phillips-Divorce, 1950-1955 (Box 448, Folder 10)
    - No. 270: Mable LeBlanc and E.C. LeBlanc-Estate-Insanity, 1950 (Box 449, Folder 1)
    - No. 272: Daisy L. Riley, 1950 (Box 449, Folder 2)
    - No. 273: P.T. Kilman-Accounts, 1950-1951 (Box 449, Folder 3)
    - No. 274: Effie McCoy-Divorce, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 4)
    - No. 277: Anderson County, 1951-1952 (Box 449, Folder 5)
    - No. 278: Henderson County, 1951-1952 (Box 449, Folder 6)
    - No. 279: Madge Bloxon (Lynch)-Frankston, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 7)
    - No. 282A: Houston County-State of Texas v. Robert Jones, 1951-1952 (Box 449, Folder 8)
    - No. 282B: Houston County, Beaumont, TX (Abortion), 1951-1952 (Box 449, Folder 9)
    - No. 283: Mrs. Ruby Mahaney, 1950-1951 (Box 449, Folder 10)
    - No. 285: Katie Myrl Adams-Guardianship, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 11)
    - No. 287: Carrie Boswell-Compensation, 1951-1952 (Box 449, Folder 12)
    - No. 288: Maurice Wheat-Will, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 13)
    - No. 289: J. Carlyon Brewer-Tax Protest, 1946-1950 (Box 449, Folder 14)
    - No. 293: Ray & Willie Parker, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 15)
    - No. 294: Style Shop-Mrs. Dowdy, 1950 (Box 449, Folder 16)
    - No. 295: Bill Pirtle, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 17)
    - No. 296: Floyd McCuin-Divorce, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 18)
    - No. 297: B.J. Rountree, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 19)
    - No. 298: James Sowers-Liquor Injunction, 1950-1951 (Box 449, Folder 20)
    - No. 299: R.C. Shamburger, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 21)
    - No. 301: Rebekah Jane McNeill (Hays)-Divorce, 1951 (Box 449, Folder 22)
    - No. 304: E.L. Stevenson-Divorce, 1952 (Box 449, Folder 23)
    - No. 307: Clifford Pelham, Eustace Feed & Seed, 1953-1954 (Box 449, Folder 24)
    - No. 309: Mr. & Mrs. E.G. Hickman-Wills, 1958 (Box 449, Folder 25)
    - No. 310: Bessie Taylor Parker-Divorce, 1953 (Box 449, Folder 26)
    - E. (Elbert) Cason v. Travelers Insurance Company, 1937 (Box 449, Folder 27)
    - Rebecca Warner v. A.C Barton, 1938 (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - Roy Jones, 1945 (Box 450, Folder 2)
    - Title Options, 1945-1948, 1966 (Box 450, Folder 3)
    - Trial Against Will Lee & Marie Steen for the Murder of Terry Steen, 1945-1947 (Box 450, Folder 4)
    - Dave McGee, Jack Pinkston v. Mrs. H.W. Wills, 1947-1950 (Box 450, Folder 5)
    - Muriel Bryant v. E.F. Bryant (Divorce), 1948 (Box 450, Folder 6)
    - J.C. Allen v. W.B. Hinton, 1949 (Box 450, Folder 7)
    - J.C. Allen v. W.B. Hinton (Damages), 1949 (Box 450, Folder 8)
    - J.C. Allen v. W.B. Hinton (Wages), 1949 (Box 450, Folder 9)
    - Ernest M. Brewer v. Fidelity & Casualty Company of N.Y., 1949 (Box 451, Folder 1)
    - J.M. Crawford v. Alamo Casualty Company, 1949 (Box 451, Folder 2)
    - Grand Jury, 1949 (Box 451, Folder 3)
    - Johnnie E. Lester-Child Custody, 1949-1956 (Box 451, Folder 4)
    - M.B. Davis, 1950 (Box 451, Folder 5)
    - Lilla Blythe (Mrs. H.E.), 1951 (Box 451, Folder 6)
    - Everett Burns, 1951 (Box 451, Folder 7)
    - Alton Paris-Murder Trial, 1951 (Box 451, Folder 8)
    - Alton Paris-Murder Trial (Photographs Included), 1951 (Box 451, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 451, Folder 10)
    - H.W. West Before Grand Jury (shorthand), 1945 December 1 (Box 451, Folder 11)
  - Media, 1952-1988, undated; 4
    Index Terms
    Genres
    16 mm motion picture film; 8 mm motion picture; Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Photographic print; Reel to reel tapes; Video home system (VHS) tapes
    - Audio, 200 Years of Growth and Progress in America” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 1)
    - Audio, Appointed Chairman of Select Subcommittee to Investigate the Crime Situation in the District of Columbia [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 2)
    - Audio, Approval of President’s Views on Vietnam [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 3)
    - Audio, Campaign Advertisement for John Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 518, Folder 4)
    - Audio, Campaign Commercials [Reel-to-Reel], 1968 (Box 518, Folder 5)
    - Audio, Campaign Songs “Talk” and “Sing” song [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 518, Folder 6)
    - Audio, Churchill, Winston S.: Excerpts from the 12-Record Set. His Memoirs and Speeches. [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 7)
    - Audio, Clark [Cassette], 1974 (Box 518, Folder 8)
    - Audio, Clark phone call [Cassette], 1973 January 3 (Box 518, Folder 9)
    - Audio, “Colored People” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 10)
    - Audio, “Compromise and Courage”, undated (Box 518, Folder 11)
    - Audio, “Congressional Election and Block Voting” [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 518, Folder 12)
    - Audio, “Continued Development and Employment of Safeguard Missiles...” from Washington, Senator Tower [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 13)
    - Audio, Conversation Dealing with the Trial (cannot understand) [Cassette], circa 1973 (Box 518, Folder 14)
    - Audio, Cook, Bill and Family [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 15)
    - Audio, Dowdy Song, Composed and Sung by Lynn Pixley [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 518, Folder 16)
    - Audio, “The Federal Government is Huge” [Reel-to-Reel], 1972 (Box 518, Folder 17)
    - Audio, Federal Urban Renewal Program [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 18)
    - Audio, “Foreign Aid, Tax Increases, and DeficiBt Spending” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 19)
    - Audio, Honorable John Dowdy Member of Congress: “The Leading Question,” CBS Radio Network [LP], 1960 February (Box 518, Folder 20)
    - Audio, J. D. Dowdy Jingle [Reel-to-Reel], 1972 April 6 (Box 518, Folder 21)
    - Audio, John Dowdy for U.S. Congress: 1. Serious Problem, 2. (Folder 22)
    - Intelligent Govt., 3. Foe of Waste, 4. Seniority, 5. (Folder 23)
    - Prosperity, 6. Vietnam, 7. Crime, 8. Dowdy Song [LP], 1968 (Box 518, Folder 22)
    - Audio, John Dowdy Political Spots [LP], 1962 (Box 518, Folder 23)
    - Audio, Kilgore, Joe and Spots from Charley Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 518, Folder 24)
    - Audio, Last Report of 88th Congress [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 25)
    - Audio, NASA Special Report #50 Apollo-8 Mission [Reel-to-Reel], 1968 December (Box 518, Folder 26)
    - Audio, “Operation Abolition” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 27)
    - Audio, Pazornik, Elaine-Juror Questioning [Cassette], 1972 (Box 518, Folder 28)
    - Audio, Phone Conversation John Dowdy and Tom Herman [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 29)
    - Audio, Phone conversation Nathan Cohen and John Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1970 January 13 (Box 518, Folder 30)
    - Audio, Phone conversation Nathan Cohen and John Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1970 January 19 (Box 518, Folder 31)
    - Audio, Phone conversation Nathan Cohen and John Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1970 January 28 (Box 518, Folder 32)
    - Audio, Rabinovich, Rabbi Emauel, “Plans of Synagogue of Satan” (dictation). [Cassette], 1953 January 12 (Box 518, Folder 33)
    - Audio, Radio Spots [Reel-to-Reel], 1972 April 6 (Box 518, Folder 34)
    - Audio, “Slick Trick” [Reel-to-Reel], 1966 (Box 518, Folder 35)
    - Audio, Speech to Farm Bureau [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 36)
    - Audio, Speech Upon the Adjournment of the 88th Congress [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 37)
    - Audio, Statement by Juror 24 Hours After Verdict [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 38)
    - Audio, Steele, Thomas Interview: Christmas Special [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 39)
    - Audio, Students Riots in San Francisco during House Meeting of Un-American Activities Committee [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 40)
    - Audio, Thompson, Gerald-Juror Questioning [Cassette], 1972 January 3 (Box 518, Folder 41)
    - Audio, “Vomit” Spot and Republican Tax Spot with John Bass [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 42)
    - Audio, “What We Can Do about Bad Things in America?” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 518, Folder 43)
    - Audio, “What We Want Our Government to Do for Us” [Reel-to-Reel], 1972 (Box 518, Folder 44)
    - Audio, “American Values have been Abandoned” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 1)
    - Audio, Are you for Dowdy? Campaign Song [Cassette, CD, LP, Reel-to-Reel], 1966 (Box 519, Folder 2)
    - Audio, Are you for Dowdy? Introduction to Re-election speech. “This is your Congressman, John Dowdy, asking for your vote...” [Reel-to-Reel], 1966 (Box 519, Folder 3)
    - Audio, “As Another Election Nears...” [Reel-to-Reel], 1968 (Box 519, Folder 4)
    - Audio, Bainbridge, Georgia Chamber of Commerce [Reel-to-Reel], 1967 January 21 (Box 519, Folder 5)
    - Audio, Cagle, D. P. [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 6)
    - Audio, Campaign Advertisement Dowdy-Musselwhite [Reel-to-Reel], 1962 (Box 519, Folder 7)
    - Audio, Campaign Kickoff Barbecue [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 519, Folder 8)
    - Audio, Campaign, Five 5-Minute Programs, “Asking for Support in Re- election” [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 (Box 519, Folder 9)
    - Audio, Carter’s Acceptance Speech [Reel-to-Reel], 1976 (Box 519, Folder 10)
    - Audio, “Communist Cancer Continues to Spread” [Reel-to-Reel], 1961 March (Box 519, Folder 11)
    - Audio, Federal Reserve-Wally Butterworth and Drugs-W. Cleon Skonsen [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 12)
    - Audio, Freedman, Ben at MOWW Meeting [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 13)
    - Audio, Gale Show [Reel-to-Reel], 1967 June 22 (Box 519, Folder 14)
    - Audio, Henderson County Appreciation Dinner- Eve of Re-election [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 15)
    - Audio, Johnson, Lyndon on Outer Space Achievements [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 16)
    - Audio, Lynn Pixley Introduction for Re-election Speech. “Based on the Record I Have Made...” [Reel-to-Reel], 1966 (Box 519, Folder 17)
    - Audio, Midway Crash-Watergate [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 18)
    - Audio, New Orleans, LA, “Opposition to Urban Renewal: An Agency Without a Heart” [Reel-to-Reel], 1967 April 30 (Box 519, Folder 19)
    - Audio, Phone conversation Nathan Cohen and John Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1970 January 20 (Box 519, Folder 20)
    - Audio, Pixley Campaign Songs [Reel-to-Reel], 1966 (Box 519, Folder 21)
    - Audio, “Problems Facing Americans” [Reel-to-Reel], 1970 August 23 (Box 519, Folder 22)
    - Audio, Real Estate Convention [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 23)
    - Audio, “Respectfully Asking for Your Support in My Bid for Re-election” [Reel-to-Reel], 1968 (Box 519, Folder 24)
    - Audio, Rockford, Illinois Event, Mr. Curtis, Mr. Anderson Mr. Alger, Mr. Dowdy [Reel-to-Reel], 1964 March 6 (Box 519, Folder 25)
    - Audio, Sales Meeting [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 26)
    - Audio, San Antonio Farm Bureau [Reel-to-Reel], 1962 November (Box 519, Folder 27)
    - Audio, Speech (Tape speed is too fast) [Reel-to-Reel], 1968 (Box 519, Folder 28)
    - Audio, Speech to Texas Farm Bureau [Reel-to-Reel], 1960 (Box 519, Folder 29)
    - Audio, Sunday Contact on WAVA Radio [Reel-to-Reel], 1968 (Box 519, Folder 30)
    - Audio, Television discussion program John Dowdy and John Gunther [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 31)
    - Audio, “Tendency to Glamorize So-Called Intellectuals” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 32)
    - Audio, Tepka, Otto “Unfurled” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 33)
    - Audio, “Values and Ideals are Being Changed” [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 34)
    - Audio, “Values and Ideals are Being Changed” Part 2 [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 35)
    - Audio, Waterloo, Iowa. Citizens Protesting Urban Renewal to Officials [Reel-to-Reel], undated (Box 519, Folder 36)
    - Audio, Reel-to-Reel Recorder, undated (Box 527, Folder 1)
    - Video, J. D. Dowdy #7-30 [2” reel], 1974 April 24 (Box 520, Folder 1)
    - Video, John Dowdy [VHS], 1959 (Box 520, Folder 2)
    - Video, John Dowdy for Congress [8mm film], undated (Box 520, Folder 3)
    - Video, John Dowdy 6 cuts [2” reel], 1972 April 10 (Box 521, Folder 1)
    - Video, John Dowdy Program Insert [2” reel], 1972 April 17 (Box 521, Folder 2)
    - Video, Operation Ivy: Detonation of 1st H-Bomb; Film Introduction by Dowdy (added later); Footage by Eisenhower [VHS], 1952 (Box 521, Folder 3)
    - Video, Operation Ivy: Detonation of 1st H-Bomb; Film Introduction by Dowdy (added later); Footage by Eisenhower [16mm film], 1952 (Box 522, Folder 1)
    - Video, TV spot #101: Federal Gas Tax; Inflation [16mm film], 1959 February 13 (Box 522, Folder 2)
    - Video, TV spot #196: Deficit and Inflation [16mm film], 1959 February 26 (Box 522, Folder 3)
    - Video, TV spot #323: Communist Subversion; States’ Rights Bill [16mm film], 1959 March 13 (Box 522, Folder 4)
    - Video, TV spot #438: Centralization of Federal Power [16mm film], 1959 March 26 (Box 522, Folder 5)
    - Video, TV spot #513: Pornography [16mm film], 1959 April 10 (Box 522, Folder 6)
    - Video, TV spot #698: Foreign Aid [16mm film], 1959 May 1 (Box 522, Folder 7)
    - Video, TV spot #821: States Rights Bill (HR 3) [16mm film], 1959 May 15 (Box 522, Folder 8)
    - Video, TV spot #931: Federal Dictatorship [16mm film], 1959 May 29 (Box 523, Folder 9)
    - Video, TV spot #931: Federal Dictatorship [16mm film], 1959 May 29 (Box 523, Folder 9B)
    - Video, TV spot #1042: World Court; Small Government Principles [16mm film], 1959 June 12 (Box 523, Folder 10)
    - Video, TV spot #1042: World Court; Small Government Principles [16mm film], 1959 June 12 (Box 523, Folder 10B)
    - Video, TV spot #1170: States Rights Bill (HR 3) [16mm film], 1959 June 26 (Box 523, Folder 11)
    - Video, TV spot #1284: Supreme Court & Morality/Free Speech [16mm film], 1959 July 10 (Box 523, Folder 12)
    - Video, TV spot #1466: Racketeering & Labor Reform; Civil Rights Bill [16mm film], 1959 July 31 (Box 523, Folder 13)
    - Video, TV spot #1689: Labor Racketeering [16mm film], 1959 August 28 (Box 523, Folder 14)
    - Video, TV spot #1793: Reducing Taxes, Foreign Aid & Bureaucracy, Fiscal Responsibility [16mm film], 1959 September 11 (Box 523, Folder 15)
    - Video, TV spot #2019: Inflation & Government Spending; Cornerstones of Freedom [16mm film], 1960 January (Box 523, Folder 16)
    - Video, TV spot #2119: Soviet Missiles & Defense; Character of American Citizens [16mm film], 1960 January (Box 523, Folder 17)
    - Video, TV spot #2177: Pornography [16mm film], 1960 February (Box 523, Folder 18)
    - Video, TV spot #2310: Federal spending [16 mm film, DVD, mp3], 1960 February (Box 523, Folder 19)
    - Video, TV spot #250: Campaign platform [16mm film], 1960 March (Box 523, Folder 20)
    - Video, TV spot #2597: Civil Rights Bill; Federal Spending [16mm film], 1960 March (Box 523, Folder 21)
    - Video, TV spot #2598: Campaign Issues [16mm film], 1960 March (Box 523, Folder 22)
    - Video, TV spot #2600: Corpus Christi Water Plan [16mm film], 1960 March (Box 524, Folder 23)
    - Video, TV spot #2936: Federal Encroachments on Freedom [16mm film], 1960 May 21 (Box 524, Folder 24)
    - Video, TV spot #3017: Reconnaissance Plane over Russia; HUAC [16mm film], 1960 June (Box 524, Folder 25)
    - Video, TV spot #3095: Foreign aid [16mm film], 1960 June (Box 524, Folder 26)
    - Video, Testimonial Dinner at Hotel Fredonia (no audio) [16mm film], 1961 January 7 (Box 524, Folder 27)
    - Video, TV spot #3769: Unemployment; Taxes [16mm film], 1961 February (Box 524, Folder 28)
    - Video, TV spot #3865: Proposed education dept.; world communism [16mm film], 1961 February (Box 524, Folder 29)
    - Video, TV spot #3975: Unemployment; Aid to Yugoslavia [16mm film], 1961 March (Box 524, Folder 30)
    - Video, TV spot #4077: Insanity plea; Congo; Federal Education Aid; Foreign Aid [16mm film], 1961 March (Box 524, Folder 31)
    - Video, TV spot #4184: Citizen Responsibilities & Complacency; State Department Policy [16mm film], 1961 April (Box 524, Folder 32)
    - Video, TV spot #4264: Manned Soviet Rocket; Castro; American Communism [16mm film], 1961 April (Box 524, Folder 33)
    - Video, TV spot #4375: World Communism [16mm film, DVD, mp3], 1961 May (Box 524, Folder 34)
    - Video, TV spot #4501: Subversive Groups; State Department [16mm film], 1961 May (Box 524, Folder 35)
    - Video, TV spot #4651: Castro and State Department [16mm film], 1961 June (Box 524, Folder 36)
    - Video, TV spot #4774: President Setting Tax Rates; Berlin; Treason in State Department [16mm film], 1961 June (Box 524, Folder 37)
    - Video, TV spot #4874: Pornography [16mm film], 1961 July (Box 524, Folder 38)
    - Video, TV spot #4966: Berlin Crisis [16mm film], 1961 July (Box 524, Folder 39)
    - Video, TV spot #5135: Cuban Hijackers [16mm film, DVD, mp3], 1961 August (Box 525, Folder 40)
    - Video, TV spot #5281: Foreign Aid [16mm film], 1961 August (Box 525, Folder 41)
    - Video, TV spot #5409: Socialism and Bureaucracy vs. State and Individual rights [16mm film], 1961 September (Box 525, Folder 42)
    - Video, TV spot #5872: Free Postage for Communist Propaganda [16mm film], 1962 January-February (Box 525, Folder 43)
    - Video, TV spot #6439: Re-election Campaign; NASA [16mm film, mp3], 1962 (Box 525, Folder 44)
    - Video, TV spot #6440: Campaign Opposition; COPE, and more [16mm film, mp3], 1962 (Box 525, Folder 45)
    - Video, TV spot #6441: Re-election Campaign [16mm film, mp3], 1962 (Box 525, Folder 46)
    - Video, TV spot #3203: Illegal Election Activities in 1962 Primary [16mm film, mp3], 1964 (Box 525, Folder 47)
    - Video, TV spot #3204: Radical Groups Support for Primary Opponent [16mm film, mp3], 1964 (Box 525, Folder 48)
    - Video, TV spot #179: Re-election Campaign (only positive includes campaign song sung by Glen Pixley at beginning and end of film; negative head shot of Dowdy during song on separate reel with no audio) [16mm film, mp3], 1966 (Box 525, Folder 49)
    - Video, TV spot #179: Re-election Campaign (only positive includes campaign song sung by Glen Pixley at beginning and end of film; negative head shot of Dowdy during song on separate reel with no audio) [16mm film, mp3], 1966 (Box 525, Folder 49B)
    - Video, TV spot #5310-1: Re-election; Vietnam, Inflation, Crime, Taxes, Foreign Aid [16mm film, mp3], 1968 (Box 525, Folder 51)
    - Video, TV spot #5310-2: Re-election; Seniority, Foreign Aid, Nuclear Defense, Inflation, Taxes, Riots, Vietnam [16mm film, mp3], 1968 (Box 525, Folder 52)
    - Video, Home movie (extremely poor condition, possibly unrepairable) [16mm film], undated (Box 525, Folder 53)
    - Photographs, Adult Basic Education Graduation, Crockett, TX, 1968 (Box 451A, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, American Dairy Princess Susanne Bradford, 1966 (Box 451A, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, Americans for Constitutional Action, 1966 (Box 451A, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, Athens High School Students, 1952-1953 (Box 451A, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, Atlas Hotels, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 451A, Folder 5)